

Arnulfo Israel Ramos Magaña

Software Engineer

Contact Information

Email: arnulfo_israel@hotmail.com

Github: https://israelramosm.github.io/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/israel-ramos/

Phone: 3411362414

Profile

I worked in different technologies and projects and I like to use different kinds of languages and frameworks. I have worked in C#, a bit of React and Angular, and right now I am working in a backend project using java.

Technical Skills

Technologies

- HTML5
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Bootstrap
- JQuery
- C#
- .NET Core

- ASP.NET
- Java
- Node
- Webpack
- Expressjs
- AngularJS
- TypeScript
- Git
- REST

Certifications

 App Builder, Microsoft Certified Professional Web Applications, Microsoft Certified Professional

Work Experience

Tata Consuntancy Services - Developer

Feb 2019 – today

- Working on a backend project using java
- Involved in internal projects
- Working the Learning and Development team to organize and give sessions about the technologies and tools that we constantly use in the workspace

Unosquare – Software Engineer

Mar 2017 - Ago 2018

- Made a static website using HTML5, JS, CSS3, jQuery, bootstrap and .NET with C#
- Worked on several opened source projects using frameworks like angular, Typescript,
 React and configurations with webpack, I also did unit testing
- Used C# with .NET and .NET Core, usually making modifications that required changes to the API and connection to a Database. I also did unit testing.

Unosquare – Internship

Sep 2016 – Mar 2017

• Was preparing and passed the certification test form Microsoft 480, 486 and 487.

Education

Guadalajara University – Telematics Enginner

Jan 2013 – Dec 2016

• Cisco Networking Academy

Languages

Spanish – Mother Tongue English - Intermediate